https://www.haslemerehockey.com/privacy-policy/

Membership
Teamo HELP!
Membership
Teamo HELP!
HHC Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Haslemere Hockey Club uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.
Haslemere Hockey Club is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Haslemere Hockey Club may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 2014
What We Collect
We may collect the following information:
Name
Contact information including email address and postcode.
Demographic information such as preferences and interests.
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email or post. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How We Use Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. If you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links To Other Websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to our registered address or emailing us at admin@haslemerehockey.com
We will not sell, lease or distribute your email address to third parties unless we are required by law to do so. We will not use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties you may find interesting unless you explictly tell us that you wish for this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 & the more recently introduced/refined General Data Protection Regulation Act (GDPR). If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us at admin@haslemerehockey.com
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, or if you wish us to remove your data from our system, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect, and/or process the deletion of your data if requested.
Last updated 16th May 2018
–
Registration & Member/Team Management Register to become a member Get news & updates
News & Views
Club House Covid Protocols
HHC Club Day – 5th September 2020
How to “Email your group” using Teamo
Session RegistrationNeeded for “Track & Trace”
Haslemere Hockey Club.
Woolmer Hill Sports Ground, Woolmer Hill Rd, Haslemere GU27 1QA, UK
© 2020 Haslemere Hockey Club - Hampshire, Surrey, W Sussex All rights reserved.
We use cookies to enhance your site experience, improve our understanding analysing our site traffic finally to enable social media features.
By continuing to browse, closing this banner, scrolling or clicking a link you agree to the use of cookies.AcceptRefuseCookie Policy
Revoke cookies
